

VICTORIA AFUA ADOBEA ASAMOAH

P. O. BOX 667, KANESHIE-ACCRA

B49/12 Dr Busia High Street, Odorkor-Accra. GA-532-9215

Mobile: +233 (0) 554705775, Email: Vasamoah55@gmail.com

PROFILE

I am a highly motivated Business Administration graduate, who seeks to be in a growing organization or institution, where I can get the opportunities to prove my abilities by accepting challenges and fulfilling organizational goals through continuous learning and commitment, and in the process, acquire new experiences that enrich my professional competence. I am a fast learner who easily adapts to new and ever-changing work environment, and is open for further training and modeling.

CAREER OBJECTIVE

Having a Bachelor's degree in Business Administration, accounting major, without much experience in the field, I seek for opportunities to further expand my professional knowledge, skills and qualifications.

As a novice to the world of technology, I want to use what I learn, gain knowledge from experts, and contribute or work on creative initiatives that push the boundaries of technology. Along with my demonstrated technical expertise and teamwork abilities, I also provide a strong work ethic.

EDUCATIONAL BACKGROUND

University of Ghana - Legon, Ghana Bsc. Business Administration 2019 - 2023

Wesley Girls' Senior High School - Cape Coast, Ghana General Arts 2016 - 2019

Pastor Abaidoo Preparatory School - Accra, Ghana **Basic Education** 2013 - 2016

WORKING EXPERIENCE

NATIONAL SERVICE PERSONNEL

January 2024 - Date

NATIONAL SERVICE HEAD OFFICE

AIRPORT RESIDENTIAL AREA

- Training in data analytics.
- Training in database management (SQL).
- Training in Microsoft Excel and Power BI.
- Training in UI/UX design.
- Training in flutter.

INTERNSHIP

October 2022 – December 2022

ASA SAVINGS AND LOANS

ODORKOR-ACCRA, GHANA

- Assisting with deposits and withdrawals.
- Assisting with collection of loans.
- Customer care personnel.
- Marketing and sales of company products.

PRODUCTION ASSISTANT/PRESENTER

2021 - 2022

AFRONOVA RADIO

ACCRA, GHANA

- Undertaking general research for programs.
- Assisting with time keeping and the recording of transmissions.
- Supporting the production team.
- Contributing to the creative input of a show (writing cues and updating scripts).
- Researching news stories and pitching new ideas.
- Presenting shows or small sections of a program.

PERSONAL SKILLS

- In-depth skills in web-based application and proficient in the use of Microsoft Office Suite.
- Effective communication abilities and presentation skills.
- Strong quantitative and analytical skills.
- Knowledge in database management (SQL).
- Great leadership skills.
- Integrity, honesty, time management and teamwork are also personal professional attitudes.

LEADERSHIP EXPERIENCE

PENSA LEGON BUSINESS AND POLITICAL CHAMBER

• Financial Secretary (2021-2023)

BSC. BUSINESS ADMINISTRATION

• Assistant Course Representative (2022)

WESLEY GIRLS' SENIOR HIGH SCHOOL

- Executive Secretary Child's Right (2018 2019)
- Dorm Monitor (2018 2019)
- Sales Representative (2018 2019)
- Coordinator (2018)
- Chapel Representative (2019)

VOLUNTEER ACTIVITIES

- Auxilia Foundation Organize fundraisers and donations for orphanages. (2017 Present)
- Member of Arts Club.
- Sunday School Teacher Church of Pentecost. (2017 Present)

REFERENCES

 Mr. Ebenezer Zotoo Staff Officer National Service Secretariat Accra-Ghana

Mail: Ebenzotoo@gmail.com

Mr. Eric Agyei
 Loan Officer
 ASA Savings and Loans
 Accra-Ghana
 Tel: 233 (0) 24 954 0668